buzzcity.com 2015-06-13

# BuzzCity - Mobile Internet Advertising

By continuing to use this site, you consent the use of cookies on your device or browser as described in our Cookie Policy unless you have disabled them. You can change your cookie settings at any time but most parts of our site will not work without them. 

This privacy statement (“Privacy Policy”) explains how information is collected, shared and utilized by BuzzCity (“BuzzCity”, or “we”, “us”, “our”), BuzzCity subsidiaries and affiliated companies. This Privacy Policy applies to the BuzzCity website at [buzzcity.com](http://www.buzzcity.com/) and other online services operated by BuzzCity. If you have any concerns about privacy on the site, please send an email to [dpo@buzzcity.com](mailto:dpo@buzzcity.com) and we will try to address it.

Our Privacy Policy explains:

  * What information we collect and why we collect it.
  * How we use that information.
  * The choices we offer, including how to access and update information.

At BuzzCity, we keep it as simple as possible, but if you are not familiar with terms such as cookies, IP address, pixel tags and browsers, then read about these Key Terms.

### Information collected by BuzzCity

We receive and store personal information that you choose to enter on our site, or provide to us in any other ways, such as by telephone or by electronic mail or by survey. We receive these information about you – including basic stuff like which language you speak, to more complex information like which ads you will find most useful – from online and offline sources in order to provide our users with a better experience and to improve the overall quality of BuzzCity services.

BuzzCity collect the following types of information:

**_Information given by you to BuzzCity_**
    * When you sign up for a new BuzzCity Account or when you register for any of our services, we collect personal information about you that may include your name, address, email address and telephone number.
    * We may combine the information that you submit on our site with information about you with a better experience and improve overall BuzzCity services.
    * In addition, if you voluntarily complete a detailed publisher or advertiser profile, we collect personal information about you as part of that profile. This information may include your name, address, birthday and contact information, as well as general information about your organisation or business, where applicable.
**_Information that BuzzCity automatically collect_**

We may collect information about the services that you use and how you use them, when you visit a website that uses our content or advertising services or when you view and interact with our content or advertising.

    * **Device information**

We may collect device-specific information, such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information including phone number.

    * **Log information**

When you use our services or view content provided by BuzzCity, we may collect and store certain information in server logs. This may include:

      * Details of how you used our service, such as your search queries.
      * BuzzCity utilizes cookies to automatically collect information about visitors to our site. The cookies from our site do not collect personal information. However, we may combine information collected through certain cookies we issue in our site with other personal information that you provided to us on the site.
      * We may collect information using pixel tags. Pixel tags may be used to deliver cookies, count visits, and understand the usage and activity on the site and to tell if an electronic mail has been opened and acted upon.
      * We automatically receive and store other types of informationwhenever you interact with us. For example, we will track the typeof web browser you are using, where you pages which you link from the site. 
    * **Local Storage**
      * We may collect and store information, including personal information, locally on your device using technologies such as, but not limited to, browser web storage (including HTML5) and application data caches.
    * **Cookies and anonymous identifiers**
      * We use various technologies to collect and store information when you visit a BuzzCity service, and this may include sending one or more cookies or anonymous identifiers to your device. We also use cookies and anonymous identifiers when you interact with services we offer to our partners, such as BuzzCity content or advertising services that may appear on other sites.

We may also collect information in connection with our desktop or mobile services provided to publishers and advertisers as described below under the Desktop/ Mobile Services.

**_How BuzzCity use information we collect_**

We use the information we collect from all of our services to provide, maintain, protect and improve them, to develop new services, and to protect BuzzCity and our users. On top of that, we use this information to offer you tailored content. For example, we may utilize your information to:

    * Operate and improve our site and services. Example: We use information collected from cookies and other technologies, like pixel tags, to improve your user experience and the overall quality of our services. For example, by saving your language preferences, we may be able to have our services appear in the language you prefer. When showing you tailored ads, we will not associate a cookie or anonymous identifier with sensitive categories, such as those based on race, religion, sexual orientation or health condition. 
    * Respond to your comments and provide customer service. Example: When you contact BuzzCity, we may keep a record of your communication to help resolve any issues that you might be facing. We may also use your email address to provide and deliver products and services and send you related information, including confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, security advisories, and support and administrative messages. 
    * Protect the rights or property of BuzzCity or our users.
    * We may combine personal information from one service with information that includes personal information, from other BuzzCity services – for example, to make it easier to share things with people you know.
    * We will ask for your consent before using information for a purpose not related to those that are set out in this Privacy Policy.
    * Communicate with you about promotions, events, and other news about products and services offered by BuzzCity and our partners.
    * BuzzCity processes personal information on our servers in many countries around the world. We may process your personal information on a server located outside the country where you live.

### Transparency and choice

People have different privacy concerns. Our goal is to be clear about what information we collect, so that you can make meaningful choices about how it is used. You may also set your browser to delete or block all cookies, including cookies associated with our services, or to indicate when a cookie is being set. However, it is important to note that many of our services will not work properly or function as intended if any of the cookies are disabled.

### Sharing of personal information

BuzzCity does not share your personal information with third-parties except as approved by you or described below:

  * **With your consent:** When you agree to our sharing your information, for example, with other third-parties for their own marketing purposes subject to their separate privacy policies.
  * **Agents and Service Providers:** BuzzCity may engage other companies and individuals to perform services on our behalf. Example of such services includes processing credit card payments, sending postal mail and electronic mail to you and analysing the data. While these agents and services may have access to your personal information in connection with the performance of services for BuzzCity, they may not use such information for any purpose other than providing such services to BuzzCity and based on our instructions and in compliance with appropriate privacy, confidentiality and security measures.
  * **Protection of BuzzCity and Others:** We release account and other personal information when we believe that release is necessary or appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our user Agreements, or protect the rights, property, or safety of BuzzCity, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for security, fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
  * **Corporate Transfers and Financings:** BuzzCity may share your personal information in connection with any merger, sale of BuzzCity assets, or a financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.
  * **Aggregate information:** BuzzCity may share aggregate information, non-personally identifiable information about you and/or your customers with advertisers, publishers, business partners, sponsors and other third-parties. For example, we may share information publicly to show trends about the general use of our services.

### Security of personal information you provide

BuzzCity take reasonable measures to protect your personal information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. BuzzCity cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information that BuzzCity receives.

In particular: 

  * We encrypt many of our services using SSL.
  * We review our information collection, storage and processing practices, including physical security measures, to guard unauthorized access to systems.
  * We restrict access to personal information to BuzzCity employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us, and who are subject to contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.

### BuzzCity Desktop/ Mobile Services

BuzzCity provides desktop/ mobile advertising services (“Desktop/ Mobile Services”) to advertisers and publishers. If you are a publisher using BuzzCity Desktop/ Mobile Services, BuzzCity may access, index, and cache requests made from your desktop/ mobile sites, applications, and device platforms to our system, including by automated means. In the course of providing these Desktop/ Mobile services, BuzzCity collects aggregate data from publisher sites and uses such data for a number of purposes, including, but not limited to, providing publishers, advertisers and others with aggregate information about traffic and site usage in our advertising network.

BuzzCity also collects certain information about visitors to publisher sites that connect to our Desktop/ Mobile Services. BuzzCity will automatically collect and receive information about those visitors such as, but not limited to, browser identifiers, session information, browser cookies, device type, carrier provider, IP address, unique device ID, carrier user ID, geo-location information, sites visited and clicks on content or advertising we display. BuzzCity may track information over time and over multiple publisher sites and use non-personally identifiable information collected from such visitors to provide reports to advertisers and others and to help us display content or advertising that may be of interest to visitors. In some cases, the network operators may send visitor phone numbers to BuzzCity. BuzzCity may use such information to perform analysis aimed at improving our services and technologies and may use this data to display content or advertising customized to visitor interests and preferences. BuzzCity does not use such information for telemarketing or to share with any third-parties for their own use. In addition, BuzzCity may collect personal information directly from customers on behalf of advertisers and periodically transfer such information to such advertisers.

### Application

Our Privacy Policy applies to all of the services offered by BuzzCity and its affiliates, including services offered through other sites such as our content or advertising services, but exclude services that have separate privacy policies that do not incorporate this Privacy Policy.

Our Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies, or individuals, including products or sites that may be displayed to you in search results, sites that include BuzzCity services, or other sites linked from our services. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices from other companies and organizations who promote our services, and who may use cookies, pixel tags and other technologies to serve and offer relevant content or advertising.

### Enforcement

We regularly review our compliance with our Privacy Policy. We also adhere to self-regulatory frameworks. We work with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with our users directly. For more details, you may refer to our Personal Data Protection Notice.

### Changes

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice including, for certain services, email notification of privacy policy changes.

* * *
